Guide to the DoubleTake Records, 1908-1999, bulk 1994-1999 RL.00321
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
DoubleTake records
1908-1999
1994-1999
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University)
Duke University. Center for Documentary Studies. DoubleTake
RL.00321
783
53.1 Linear Feet
Approximately 58,872 Items
The DoubleTake magazine records contain story manuscripts with editor's markings, correspondence, photographs and slides, and production files for issue numbers 1-16, 1994-1999. Files of editors Jay Woodruff, Rob Odom, and other editors contain correspondence with writers whose work they were interested in publishing and editing. There are postcards and transparencies used in various issues; and a complete run of the magazine through spring 1999. There are two unidentified files. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Access Restrictions
Access is restricted.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
Materials were transferred into the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 1999 and 2010.
Historical Note
The DoubleTake, magazine formerly associated with the Center for Documentary Studies at Duke University, was co-founded by Alex Harris and Robert Coles. It was established in 1995 to publish photography, fiction, poetry, and essays documenting the human experience "as it is and as it might be." In its early years, Alex Harris was responsible for managing everyday operations, while Robert Coles was based in Boston. DoubleTake's high-quality publications, focusing on photography, earned national awards and praise, including a National Magazine Award for general excellence.
Despite its successes the magazine was unable to rein in production costs. Alex Harris left the magazine in 1998, remaining with the Center for Documentary Studies as a professor and photographer. Rather than suspend publication, Coles moved the magazine to Somerville, New Jersey, where it continued to struggle financially. Its final issue, Summer 2003, was funded by a series of benefit concerts by Bruce Springsteen. By November 2004, the magazine closed its offices permanently.
Collection Overview
Collection holds story manuscripts (with editor's marks), correspondence, and production files for issues 1-16, 1994-1999. Files of editors Jay Woodruff, Rob Odom, and other editors contain correspondence with writers whose work they were interested in publishing and editing. There are postcards and transparencies used in various issues; and a complete run of the magazine through spring 1999. There are two unidentified files.
Later accessions include production files and correspondence between the magazine's editors and its contributors, also covering issues 1-16.
Accession 2010-0081 includes photographer name files, dating from 1993 (pre-production) through 1998, kept by Alex Harris and other DoubleTake staff. Files were created whenever a photographer corresponded with the magazine, and include copies of correspondence between editors and photographers, slides of sample work, contracts for those who were accepted as contributors, and occasional biographies or other information about the photographer. Some files represent a particular museum's exhibit rather than a personal photographer; these are designated with exhibit titles instead of a photographer's name.
Files are organized alphabetically, and include correspondence from well before the magazine began publication, as well as materials post-dating Harris's departure from the magazine.
Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Related Material
Related collections at Duke University's Special Collections Library include the Alex Harris Papers, the DoubleTake Magazine serial (1995-2003), and the NC Self Portrait Project (which includes some photographs included in the magazine).
American literature; American literature -- 20th century -- Periodicals; Arts, American -- 20th century -- Periodicals; Documentary Photography; Documentary Photography -- Periodicals; Editors -- United States -- Correspondence; Periodical editors -- United States -- Correspondence; Photojournalism -- Periodicals; North Carolina -- Periodicals; Photographs; Slides (photographs); Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University); Harris, Alex, 1949-
- Accession (1999-0187): DoubleTake Records, 1994-1999, 282506
  - Correspondence with Writers, 1994-1997 (bulk 1994-1995), 282526 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Jay Woodruff, Managing editor, 1994-1997
    - Correspondence A-M, 282528 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence N-Z, 282527 (Box 2)
  - Production Files, 282512
    Missing files for issues 4 and 6.
    - Issue No.1, 282525 (Box 2)
    - Issue No.2, 282524 (Box 3)
    - Issue No.3, 282523 (Box 3)
    - Issue No.5, 282522 (Box 3)
    - Issue No.7, 282521 (Box 4)
    - Issue No.8, 282520 (Box 4)
    - Issue No.9, 282519 (Box 4)
    - Issue No.10, 282518 (Box 5)
    - Issue No.11, 282517 (Box 5)
    - Issue No.12, 282516 (Box 6)
    - Issue No.13, 282515 (Box 6)
    - Issue No.14, 282514 (Box 7)
    - Issue No.15, 282513 (Box 7)
  - Executive Editor's Files, 282507 (Box 8)
    Rob Odom's office files, chiefly relating to marketing and publicity; maintained in alphabetical order.
    - A-E, 282511 (Box 8)
    - E-P, 282510 (Box 9)
    - P-W, 282509 (Box 10)
      No files X through Z.
    - Correspondence with writers, 282508 (Box 11)
      Alphabetical by writer's last name
- Accession (1999-0263): DoubleTake Records, 1908-1999, 282494
  - Production Files:, 282498 (Box 1)
    - Issue 1, 282505 (Box 1)
    - Issue 2, 282504 (Box 1)
    - Issue 3, 282503 (Box 1)
    - Issue 3, 282502 (Box 2)
    - Issue 4, 282501 (Box 2)
    - Issue 4, 282500 (Box 3)
    - Issue 6, 282499 (Box 3)
  - Prints and Transparencies/negatives, 282497 (Box 4)
    Primarily for issues 3,6,7,9-12, but possibly others
  - Postcards, 282496 (Box 5)
  - DoubleTake issues, 1-16, 282495 (Box 5)
- Accession (1999-0336): DoubleTake Records, 1994-1999, 282392
  - Production Files by issue, then author, 282393 (Box 1)
    General materials also interfiled
    - Issue 3: Winter 1996 (2 folders), 282490
      - Adam Schwartz, 282493 (Box 1)
      - Josip Novakovich, 282492 (Box 1)
      - Jonathan Veit, 282491 (Box 1)
    - Issue 4: Spring 1996 (2 folders), 282485
      - Charles Baxter, 282489 (Box 1)
      - Lee Martin, 282488 (Box 1)
      - Joyce Carol Oates, 282487 (Box 1)
      - Shipping--Label--Inventory--Advertising--Correspondence, 282486 (Box 1)
    - Issue 5: Summer 1996 (11 folders), 282472
      - Edward Hirsch, 282484 (Box 1)
      - Elliott Dark, 282483 (Box 1)
      - Rick Bass, 282482 (Box 1)
      - Peter Feibleman, 282481 (Box 1)
      - John Vachon, 282480 (Box 1)
      - Jayne Ann Phillips, 282479 (Box 1)
      - David Aronson, 282478 (Box 1)
      - Bill Hayes, 282477 (Box 1)
      - Bill McKibben, 282476 (Box 1)
      - Rafael Campo, 282475 (Box 1)
      - Reynolds Price, 282474 (Box 1)
      - Shipping--Labels--Art--Correspondence--Editorial, 282473 (Box 1)
    - Issue 6: Fall 1996 (2 folders), 282469
      - Revised pages, 282471 (Box 1)
      - Final master set, 282470 (Box 1)
    - Issue 7: Winter 1997 (3 folders), 282465
      - Master set, 282468 (Box 1)
      - "Final affected pages", 282467 (Box 1)
      - Proof, 282466 (Box 1)
    - Issue 12: Spring 1998, 282463
      - John Cheever, 282464 (Box 1)
    - Issue 13: Summer 1998 (2 folders), 282456
      - Lookmark 13, 282462 (Box 1)
      - New Views 13, 282461 (Box 1)
      - "Here" 13, 282460 (Box 1)
      - Gen. Ed., 282459 (Box 1)
      - Garden City 13, 282458 (Box 1)
      - Toni Morrison, 282457 (Box 1)
    - Issue 14: Fall 1998 (9 folders), 282399
      - Tip-on, 282455 (Box 1)
      - Captions, 282454 (Box 1)
      - Masthead 14, 282453 (Box 1)
      - Kelleen Zubick, 282452 (Box 1)
      - Czeslaw Milosz, 282451 (Box 1)
      - Susan Lasher, 282450 (Box 1)
      - Oliver Sacks, 282449 (Box 1)
      - Sven Birkerts, 282448 (Box 1)
      - Editor's note, 282447 (Box 1)
      - Kanan Makiya, 282446 (Box 1)
      - Robert Kerrey, 282445 (Box 1)
      - Bookmark 14, 282444 (Box 1)
      - There [William Carlos Williams], 282443 (Box 1)
      - Peter Brown, 282442 (Box 1)
      - New Views 14, 282441 (Box 2)
      - View finder 14, 282440 (Box 2)
      - Moment in hist. 14, 282439 (Box 2)
      - Amer. Gazetter 14, 282438 (Box 2)
      - Here [Sue Halpern] 14, 282437 (Box 2)
      - Gen. Ed., 282436 (Box 2)
      - Contributors 14, 282435 (Box 2)
      - Credits & Permissions - 14, 282434 (Box 2)
      - Editor's Story 14, 282433 (Box 2)
      - Sue Halpern, 282432 (Box 2)
      - In Progress: Beck, 282431 (Box 2)
      - In Progress: Ackerman, 282430 (Box 2)
      - In Progress: Grazda, 282429 (Box 2)
      - Sylwia Kapuscinski, 282428 (Box 2)
      - Boylston, 282427 (Box 2)
      - Lookmark, 282426 (Box 2)
      - Lawrence Diller, 282425 (Box 2)
      - Gary Whitehead, 282424 (Box 2)
      - N. Gallagher, 282423 (Box 2)
      - Alec Wilkinson, 282422 (Box 2)
      - Michael Lesy, 282421 (Box 2)
      - Nigel Pitman, 282420 (Box 2)
      - Tina Rathbone, 282419 (Box 2)
      - Ehud Havazelet, 282418 (Box 3)
      - Stephen Koch, 282417 (Box 3)
      - Barney/Verdella, 282416 (Box 3)
      - Michael Cunningham, 282415 (Box 3)
      - Xiaoda Xiao, 282414 (Box 3)
      - Ethan Canin, 282413 (Box 3)
      - Edward Hirsch, 282412 (Box 3)
      - Pattiann Rogers, 282411 (Box 3)
      - Frank X. Gaspar, 282410 (Box 3)
      - Li-Young Lee, 282409 (Box 3)
      - Robert Cording, 282408 (Box 3)
      - John Haines, 282407 (Box 3)
      - Anthony Petrosky, 282406 (Box 3)
      - Bruce Beasley, 282405 (Box 3)
      - Jeff Worley, 282404 (Box 3)
      - W.S. Merwin, 282403 (Box 3)
      - Marcos Cafagña, 282402 (Box 3)
      - Arthur Smith, 282401 (Box 3)
      - Baron Wormser, 282400 (Box 3)
    - Issue 15: Winter 1999, 282397
      - Lookmark 15, 282398 (Box 3)
    - Issue #?, 282394
      - Percy, 282396 (Box 3)
      - Hurston, 282395 (Box 3)
- Accession (2010-0081): DoubleTake Records, 1993-1998, 281241; 41 boxes
  Name files for photographers, including correspondence, slides, personal statements, and other materials. Organized alphabetically by last name or exhibit title.
  - Aaronson, Jeffrey, 282391 (Box 1)
  - Abe, Koya, 282390 (Box 1)
  - Abbott, Ken, 282389 (Box 1)
  - Abrams, Rebecca, 282388 (Box 1)
  - Ackerman, Michael, 282387 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Bobby Neel, 282386 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Cameron, 282385 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Robert, 282384 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Shelby Lee, 282383 (Box 1)
  - Agenzia Contrasto, 282382 (Box 1)
  - Aguilera-Hellweg, Max, 282381 (Box 1)
  - Ahn, Eugene, 282380 (Box 1)
  - Ahlgren, Steven, 282379 (Box 1)
  - Ainsley, Spencer, 282378 (Box 1)
  - Albanese, Gerard, 282377 (Box 1)
  - Alexandra, Sharon, 282376 (Box 1)
  - Alexanian, Nubar, 282375 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Paula, 282374 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Terry, 282373 (Box 1)
  - Alston, Kwaku, 282372 (Box 1)
  - Amaritnant, Kittipong, 282371 (Box 1)
  - Amberg, Rob, 282370 (Box 1)
  - Amnesty International, 282369 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Carla, 282368 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Jon, 282367 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Kristin, 282366 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Monika, 282365 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Ri, 282364 (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Jesse, 282363 (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Katheryn, 282362 (Box 1)
  - Anshutz, Thomas, 282361 (Box 1)
  - Antman, Fran, 282360 (Box 1)
  - Arbus, Amy, 282359 (Box 1)
  - Armory Center for the Arts, 282358 (Box 1)
  - Arnold, Wayne, 282357 (Box 1)
  - Art of Science, 282356 (Box 2)
  - Asha, G., 282355 (Box 2)
  - Ashforth, Adam, 282354 (Box 2)
  - Atkinson, Brian, 282353 (Box 2)
  - Atkinson, Jeff, 282352 (Box 2)
  - Atwood, Jane, 282351 (Box 2)
  - Auld, Lynne, 282350 (Box 2)
  - Axelbank, David, 282349 (Box 2)
  - Babis, Larry, 282348 (Box 2)
  - Baden, Karl, 282347 (Box 2)
  - Baer, Gordon, 282346 (Box 2)
  - Bailey, Robert, 282345 (Box 2)
  - Balaban, Victor, 282344 (Box 2)
  - Balboni, Margot, 282343 (Box 2)
  - Balduvino and Mines, 282342 (Box 2)
  - Ball, Gordon, 282341 (Box 2)
  - Ballen, Roger, 282340 (Box 2)
  - Balog, James, 282339 (Box 2)
  - Baltermants, Dmitri, 282338 (Box 2)
  - Bamburger, Bill, 282337 (Box 2)
  - Banasiak, John, 282336 (Box 2)
  - Bankhead, Judy, 282335 (Box 2)
  - Banuelos, Luis, 282334 (Box 2)
  - Barandiaran, Adolfo, 282333 (Box 2)
  - Barboza, Anthony, 282332 (Box 2)
  - Barker, James, 282331 (Box 2)
  - Barker, Joan, 282330 (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Ernie, 282329 (Box 2)
  - Barney, Tina, 282328 (Box 2)
  - Barrat, Martine, 282327 (Box 2)
  - Barrett, Sarah, 282326 (Box 2)
  - Bartlett, Chris, 282325 (Box 3)
  - Bartos, Adam, 282324 (Box 3)
  - Bass, Pinky, 282323 (Box 3)
  - Baugnet, Andrew, 282322 (Box 3)
  - El-Baz, Jacob, 282321 (Box 3)
  - Bazan, Ernesto, 282320 (Box 3)
  - Beahan, Virginia and Laura McPhee, 282319 (Box 3)
  - Beck, Fran Bitett, 282318 (Box 3)
  - Beckman, Robert, 282317 (Box 3)
  - Beirne, Christopher, 282316 (Box 3)
  - Belanger, Marion Hoben, 282315 (Box 3)
  - Bell, Rae, Jean, 282314 (Box 3)
  - Bellamy, Peter, 282313 (Box 3)
  - Bellerose, George, 282312 (Box 3)
  - Bello, Missy, 282311 (Box 3)
  - Benjamin, Robert, 282310 (Box 3)
  - Benson, Brian, 282309 (Box 3)
  - Benson, Eric, 282308 (Box 3)
  - Bent, Courtney, 282307 (Box 3)
  - Benzakin, Jocelyne, 282306 (Box 3)
  - Berg, Niki, 282305 (Box 3)
  - Berkeley, Taisie, 282304 (Box 3)
  - Berndt, Jerry (1 of 5 folders), 282303 (Box 3)
  - Berndt, Jerry (4 of 5 folders), 282302 (Box 4)
  - Bernstein, Rita, 282301 (Box 4)
  - Berridge, Mary (2 folders), 282300 (Box 4)
  - Berticevich, George (3 folders), 282299 (Box 4)
  - Besold, Bobbie, 282298 (Box 4)
  - Bey, Dawould, 282297 (Box 4)
  - Beyt, Gene, 282296 (Box 4)
  - Bezzubov, Sasha, 282295 (Box 4)
  - Biddle, Geoffrey, 282294 (Box 4)
  - Biferie, Dan, 282293 (Box 4)
  - Billingham, Richard, 282292 (Box 4)
  - Binder, David, 282291 (Box 4)
  - Bingham, Molly, 282290 (Box 4)
  - Bireline, George, 282289 (Box 4)
  - Blackman, Tom, 282288 (Box 4)
  - Black Star, 282287 (Box 4)
  - Blau, Dick, 282286 (Box 4)
  - Blom, Gertrude, 282285 (Box 4)
  - Bloomfield, Diana Hooper, 282284 (Box 4)
  - Blosser, Abigail, 282283 (Box 4)
  - Blue, Pat, 282282 (Box 4)
  - Bokstrom, Anna, 282281 (Box 5)
  - Book, Michael, 282280 (Box 5)
  - Borensztein, Leon, 282279 (Box 5)
  - Borowiec, Andrew, 282278 (Box 5)
  - Borrelli, Vincent (2 folders), 282277 (Box 5)
  - Bottlaender, Wendelin, 282276 (Box 5)
  - Bourcart, Jean Christian, 282275 (Box 5)
  - Bourgoignie, Lelen, 282274 (Box 5)
  - Bourguedieu, Christophe, 282273 (Box 5)
  - Bowden, Daniel, 282272 (Box 5)
  - Boyle, Christopher, 282271 (Box 5)
  - Brackenbury, Deborah, 282270 (Box 5)
  - Brailey, Kristine, 282269 (Box 5)
  - Braithwaite, Hilton, 282268 (Box 5)
  - Brazan, Joseph, 282267 (Box 5)
  - Breitenbach, Eric, 282266 (Box 5)
  - Bridges, Marilyn, 282265 (Box 5)
  - Briere, Elaine, 282264 (Box 5)
  - Brisk, Zana, 282263 (Box 5)
  - Brock, Steve, 282262 (Box 5)
  - Brodwick, Marilyn, 282261 (Box 5)
  - Brody, Jill, 282260 (Box 5)
  - Brooks, Drex, 282259 (Box 5)
  - Brooks, John, 282258 (Box 5)
  - Brouws, Jeff, 282257 (Box 5)
  - Brown, Gail, 282256 (Box 5)
  - Brown, Polly, 282255 (Box 5)
  - Brown, Turner, 282254 (Box 5)
  - Bubriski, Kevin, 282253 (Box 5)
  - Buchsbaum, Monte, 282252 (Box 5)
  - Burkard, Hans Jurgen, 282251 (Box 5)
  - Burkart, Nicole, 282250 (Box 6)
  - Buirski, Nancy, 282249 (Box 6)
  - Burke, Bill, 282248 (Box 6)
  - Burnmeister, Don, 282247 (Box 6)
  - Burns/Archive, 282246 (Box 6)
  - Bush, Alfred, 282245 (Box 6)
  - Butler, Linda, 282244 (Box 6)
  - Cafferty, Debbie Fleming (3 folders), 282243 (Box 6)
  - Cagan, Steve, 282242 (Box 6)
  - Cahill, Christina, 282241 (Box 6)
  - Calahan, Walter, 282240 (Box 6)
  - Calfee, Laura Pickett, 282239 (Box 6)
  - Calhoun, Keith, 282238 (Box 6)
  - California Museum of Photography (2 folders), 282237 (Box 6)
  - Calvin, Susan, 282236 (Box 6)
  - Camara, John, 282235 (Box 6)
  - Cambon, Claudio, 282234 (Box 6)
  - Campbell, Amanda, 282233 (Box 6)
  - Canemaker, John, 282232 (Box 6)
  - Caperton, John, 282231 (Box 6)
  - Caponigo, John Paul, 282230 (Box 6)
  - Cappetta, Angela, 282229 (Box 6)
  - Capp, Kristin, 282228 (Box 6)
  - Caprio, Melisa, 282227 (Box 6)
  - Cardwell, Keith, 282226 (Box 6)
  - Carman, Rebecca, 282225 (Box 6)
  - Carter, Keith, 282224 (Box 6)
  - Carthas, David, 282223 (Box 6)
  - Catledge, Oraien, 282222 (Box 6)
  - Caudill, Michela, 282221 (Box 6)
  - Cedrins, Inara, 282220 (Box 6)
  - Chang, Chien-Chi, 282219 (Box 6)
  - Chiang, Tracey, 282218 (Box 6)
  - Chapman, Kathy, 282217 (Box 6)
  - Chavez, Kellie, 282216 (Box 6)
  - Cheuse, Joshua, 282215 (Box 6)
  - Chornesky, Jessica, 282214 (Box 6)
  - Cialdella, Gary, 282213 (Box 6)
  - Cisneros, Roman, 282212 (Box 7)
  - Clarke, Marshall, 282211 (Box 7)
  - Clayman, Adam, 282210 (Box 7)
  - Clifford, Lisa, 282209 (Box 7)
  - Clift, William, 282208 (Box 7)
  - Clifton, Jenny, 282207 (Box 7)
  - Cober, Alan, 282206 (Box 7)
  - Cohen, John, 282205 (Box 7)
  - Cohen, Mark, 282204 (Box 7)
  - Cohen, Stewart Charles, 282203 (Box 7)
  - Colburn, Richard, 282202 (Box 7)
  - Coleman, Penny, 282201 (Box 7)
  - Collier, John, 282200 (Box 7)
  - Collier, Michael, 282199 (Box 7)
  - Conley, Beverly, 282198 (Box 7)
  - Conn, John, 282197 (Box 7)
  - Connor, Ken, 282196 (Box 7)
  - Connor, Lisa, 282195 (Box 7)
  - Connor, Lois, 282194 (Box 7)
  - Connor, Mary, 282193 (Box 7)
  - Conniff, Greg, 282192 (Box 7)
  - Cook, Diane, 282191 (Box 7)
  - Cook, Diane and Len Jenshel, Hot Spots, 282190 (Box 7)
  - Cooney, Daniel, 282189 (Box 7)
  - Cooper, Chip, 282188 (Box 7)
  - Corbett, Jack, 282187 (Box 7)
  - Costello, Michael, 282186 (Box 7)
  - Coupon, William, 282185 (Box 7)
  - Covers (Magazine covers), 282184 (Box 7)
  - Cox, Reuben, 282183 (Box 7)
  - Coyne, Nancy Ann, 282182 (Box 8)
  - Creative Visions, 282181 (Box 8)
  - Cullen, Ed, 282180 (Box 8)
  - Cuomo, Bryon, 282179 (Box 8)
  - Cuomo, Yolanda, 282178 (Box 8)
  - Curtis, John, 282177 (Box 8)
  - Cyrus, Gerald, 282176 (Box 8)
  - Dabney, Taylor, 282175 (Box 8)
  - D'Allant, Thiery, 282174 (Box 8)
  - D'Amato, Paul, 282173 (Box 8)
  - Dalzell, Patricia, 282172 (Box 8)
  - Daniels, Jim, 282171 (Box 8)
  - Dannemiller, Keith, 282170 (Box 8)
  - Davenport, Nina, 282169 (Box 8)
  - Davidson, Bruce, 282168 (Box 8)
  - Davis, Steve, 282167 (Box 8)
  - Davis, Timothy, 282166 (Box 8)
  - Davis, Townsend, 282165 (Box 8)
  - Dawson, James, 282164 (Box 8)
  - Dawson, Robert, 282163 (Box 8)
  - Day, Julia, 282162 (Box 8)
  - De Buys, Bill, 282161 (Box 8)
  - De Cesare, Donna, 282160 (Box 8)
  - Deiffel, 282159 (Box 8)
  - De Keyzer, Carl (2 folders), 282158 (Box 8)
  - Delano, Paul (2 folders), 282157 (Box 8)
  - Delevigne, Lionel, 282156 (Box 8)
  - Del Valle, Eduardo, and Mirta Gomez, 282155 (Box 8)
  - DeMari, Donna, 282154 (Box 8)
  - DeMartino, Jesse, 282153 (Box 9)
  - Dennis, W. Cameron, 282152 (Box 9)
  - Denuto, Ellen, 282151 (Box 9)
  - Desht, Martin, 282150 (Box 9)
  - De Valk, Martin, 282149 (Box 9)
  - Devereaux, Joanne, 282148 (Box 9)
  - Deverell, Bill, 282147 (Box 9)
  - Devine, 282146 (Box 9)
  - Devlin, Lucinda, 282145 (Box 9)
  - Devore, Nick, 282144 (Box 9)
  - DeWaters, Jere, 282143 (Box 9)
  - Dewey, Paul, 282142 (Box 9)
  - Dicker, Jean-Jacques, 282141 (Box 9)
  - Dicorcia, Philip-Lorca, 282140 (Box 9)
  - DiGiacomo, Melchior, 282139 (Box 9)
  - Dikeman, Deanna, 282138 (Box 9)
  - Dina, Frank, 282137 (Box 9)
  - Dijkstra, Rineke, 282136 (Box 9)
  - Dorband, Roger, 282135 (Box 9)
  - Dorfman, Elena, 282134 (Box 9)
  - Dorfman, Elsa, 282133 (Box 9)
  - Dotter, Earl, 282132 (Box 9)
  - Dow, Jim, 282131 (Box 9)
  - Drake, James, 282130 (Box 9)
  - Dreisinger, Tamara, 282129 (Box 9)
  - Drucker, Max, 282128 (Box 9)
  - DuBois, Doug, 282127 (Box 9)
  - DuBasky, Valentina, 282126 (Box 9)
  - Ducklo, Matt, 282125 (Box 9)
  - Duffy, Pamela (2 folders), 282124 (Box 9)
  - Dunlap, William, 282123 (Box 10)
  - Dykstra, Rineke, 282122 (Box 10)
  - Eades, Shelley, 282121 (Box 10)
  - Eastman, Michael, 282120 (Box 10)
  - Eberhardt, David, 282119 (Box 10)
  - Eberling, Alfred, 282118 (Box 10)
  - Edinger, Claudio, 282117 (Box 10)
  - Edwards, Beth Yarnelle, 282116 (Box 10)
  - Edwards, Jennifer, 282115 (Box 10)
  - Eggleston, William, 282114 (Box 10)
  - Eisenberg, Ethan, 282113 (Box 10)
  - Eldon, Dan (2 folders), 282112 (Box 10)
  - Emerson, Mark, 282111 (Box 10)
  - Emmett, Ioana, 282110 (Box 10)
  - Epstein, Danielle, 282109 (Box 10)
  - Epstein, Mitch (4 folders), 282108 (Box 10)
  - Engel, Scott, 282107 (Box 10)
  - Ericson, Brian, 282106 (Box 10)
  - Eubanks, Jonathon, 282105 (Box 10)
  - Eskenazi, Jason, 282104 (Box 10)
  - Evans, Terry, 282103 (Box 10)
  - Everton, MacDuff, 282102 (Box 10)
  - Ewald, Wendy (3 of 5 folders), 282101 (Box 10)
  - Ewald, Wendy (2 of 5 folders), 282100 (Box 11)
  - Fadek, Timothy, 282099 (Box 11)
  - Falco, Richard, 282098 (Box 11)
  - Faller, Marion, 282097 (Box 11)
  - Falls, Lauren, 282096 (Box 11)
  - Farrington, M. Clayton, 282095 (Box 11)
  - Fay, Kathleen, 282094 (Box 11)
  - Fee, James, 282093 (Box 11)
  - Felts, Susannah, 282092 (Box 11)
  - Fennell, Maureen, 282091 (Box 11)
  - Fentress, Sam, 282090 (Box 11)
  - Ferdinand, Roy, 282089 (Box 11)
  - Ferem, Mark, 282088 (Box 11)
  - Feresten, Peter, 282087 (Box 11)
  - Fergus, Charles, 282086 (Box 11)
  - Ferguson, Brian, 282085 (Box 11)
  - Fernandez, Rafael, 282084 (Box 11)
  - Ferrato, Donna, 282083 (Box 11)
  - Fineman, Aaron, 282082 (Box 11)
  - Fink, Larry, 282081 (Box 11)
  - Finkle, Harvey, 282080 (Box 11)
  - Fishback, Jim, 282079 (Box 11)
  - Fitch, Blake, 282078 (Box 11)
  - Fitzgerald, Evelyn, 282077 (Box 11)
  - Fitzpatrick, Tara, 282076 (Box 11)
  - Fogel, Harris, 282075 (Box 11)
  - Foote, Huger, 282074 (Box 11)
  - Forman, Susan, 282073 (Box 12)
  - Forthman, Priscilla, 282072 (Box 12)
  - Forslund, Linda, 282071 (Box 12)
  - Foster, Charles, 282070 (Box 12)
  - Fournet, Annette, 282069 (Box 12)
  - Frame, Allen, 282068 (Box 12)
  - Franco, Angel, 282067 (Box 12)
  - Franco, Ivan, 282066 (Box 12)
  - Frank, Robert, 282065 (Box 12)
  - Frankfurter, Robert, 282064 (Box 12)
  - Franklin, Joseph, 282063 (Box 12)
  - Fratkin, Leslie, 282062 (Box 12)
  - Freeman, Roland, 282061 (Box 12)
  - Freeman, Tina, 282060 (Box 12)
  - Friedman, John, 282059 (Box 12)
  - From the Hip, 282058 (Box 12)
  - Fulton, Jack, 282057 (Box 12)
  - Futterman, Marilyn S., 282056 (Box 12)
  - Gaetz, Susan, 282055 (Box 12)
  - Galindo, Roberto, 282054 (Box 12)
  - Gallagher, Carol, 282053 (Box 12)
  - Galluccio, Stephen, 282052 (Box 12)
  - Galvic, James Michael, 282051 (Box 12)
  - Gandert, Miguel, 282050 (Box 12)
  - Gardner, Dore, 282049 (Box 12)
  - Gaynor, Adam, 282048 (Box 12)
  - Gedney, William, 282047 (Box 12)
  - Gehring, Dietrich, 282046 (Box 12)
  - Gelb, Gary, 282045 (Box 12)
  - George, Dick, 282044 (Box 12)
  - Ghebreyesus, Fione, 282043 (Box 12)
  - Gholke, Robert, 282042 (Box 12)
  - Giard, Robert, 282041 (Box 12)
  - Gidel, Tim, 282040 (Box 12)
  - Giesen, Laurie, 282039 (Box 12)
  - Gil, Ricardo, 282038 (Box 12)
  - Gilden, Bruce, 282037 (Box 12)
  - Giles, Frances, 282036 (Box 12)
  - Gilden, 282035 (Box 13)
  - Gill, Stephen, 282034 (Box 13)
  - Neil, Giordano, 282033 (Box 13)
  - Gladys, 282032 (Box 13)
  - Glaser, Karen, 282031 (Box 13)
  - Glentzer, Don, 282030 (Box 13)
  - Gneiting, Robin, 282029 (Box 13)
  - Goin, Peter, 282028 (Box 13)